lovemyfire.com 2017-12-20

# LoveMyFire.com Privacy Policy

**Information We Collect**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

LoveMyFire.com only collects personally identifiable information that you provide to us and is on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number.

This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed and used to improve the content of our website, to notify our visitors of updates, and/or to respond to visitor inquiries, requests, or questions.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

 **Usage Data**

As with most other websites, LoveMyFire.com collects usage information that does not identify an individual user ("Usage Data"). For example some of the data we may automatically collect is your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), your browser used to access this site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), your operating system, the date and time of your visit to this site, and which pages you visited throughout this site.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

LoveMyFire.com uses cookies (small file placed on your computer to identify your computer, browser, and visits to our site) and web beacons (electronic file placed on a website to monitor usage). We do not use cookies or web beacons to collect personal information. Our cookies and web beacons are only used to improve the quality of our site and services.

 **Third Party Cookies**

LoveMyFire.com uses advertisements to support this site. These third-party advertising companies serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (NOT including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites, in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website: LoveMyFire.com. Google's use of the "DoubleClick DART cookie" enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

For other cookies, you can choose to disable or selectively turn off these cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with this site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

 **Google Search Box**

The search box on this web site ("Search Box") is powered by Google Inc ("Google"). You acknowledge and agree that [Google's privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) shall apply to your use of the Search Box and by using the Search Box you consent to Google using your personal data in accordance with its privacy policy.

 **Protection of Your Information**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files.

 **Third Parties**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties are believed to be trustworthy, who have a privacy policy that is consistent with ours, and who agree to keep this information confidential.

 **Third Party Links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website, or allow others to include links on this site. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. You access such third-party websites or content at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third-party website before providing any information to that website.

Since we seek to protect the integrity of our site, we welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

 **Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. By using our site you promise that you are at least 13 years old. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a child under 13 years of age, it will be deleted from our records.

 **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**

LoveMyFire.com cooperates with government and law enforcement officials to enforce and comply with the law. We may therefore disclose personal information, usage data, and any other information we have collected, if we have a good faith belief that it is reasonably necessary to (a)satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable government request, (b)enforce our [Terms of Use](http://www.lovemyfire.com/terms-copyright-disclaimer.html), including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c)detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d)protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of LoveMyFire.com, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

 **Terms and Conditions: Copyright, Disclaimer, and Disclosure**

Please also read our [Terms of Use](http://www.lovemyfire.com/terms-copyright-disclaimer.html) which establishes the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of this website, as well as our copyright and disclaimer, and disclosure.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site you consent to this site's privacy policy. If you do not agree to this privacy policy please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.

 **Managing, Correcting, or Removing Information**

We are committed to protecting your personal information. If you have submitted personal information to us and would like to update, correct, or delete the information from our records please [contact us](http://www.lovemyfire.com/contact.html).

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.

This policy was last updated on 10/23/12 to add L.L.C. to business name.

 **For Further Information**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.lovemyfire.com/contact.html).
